<Root xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/" xmlns:aid5="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/5.0/">
<?!= include("inc_cover_standard_parties", data, {cover_title:"JFDI "+data.security_type+" Agreement"}) ?>
<?!= include("inc_cover_jfdi", data, { in_series:"03" }) ?>
<Firstpage_Sidebar>
<sidebar>This document governs the investment.</sidebar>
</Firstpage_Sidebar>
<Story_Main>
  <chapter_header><?=data.security_type?> Agreement</chapter_header>
  <a_left_sidehead>Essentials </a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>Pursuant to the Founder Agreement executed on <?= data.founder_agreement_date ?> between the promoters of <?= data.company.name ?> (the &#8220;Company&#8221;) and <?!= include("inc_party", data, data.parties.investor[0]) ?> (&#8220;JFDI&#8221;), which requires the Company to <i>"authorise and issue <? if (data.jfdi_standard_valuation != false) {
  ?>convertible debt, equity, or other such security in the corporation such that, immediately prior to the Next External Financing, <?=data.company.short_name?> will own a certain percentage (the "Conversion Percentage") of the total capital in the Startup, on a fully-diluted, as-if-converted basis<? }
  else { ?><?= data.nonstandard_valuation_text ?><? } ?>"</i>;
And concurrently with the issue of Class F Shares to the founders and shareholders of the Company (&#8220;the Founders&#8221;) and of other securities to other parties with rights and interests in the Company at the time of execution of this Agreement (together, &#8220;Existing Holders&#8221;), </numbered_2_para>
  <numbered_2_para>The Company will issue, and JFDI will take up, a <?= data.security_type ?> in the total amount of <?= data.parties.investor[0].commitment?> (the "<?=data.security_type_short_singular?>"). </numbered_2_para>
  <a_left_sidehead>Definitions </a_left_sidehead>
  <para_1>In this agreement, unless the context otherwise requires:- </para_1>
  <definition>Act	means the Singapore Companies Act (Cap. 50) and includes any provision thereof as from time to time modified or re-enacted; </definition>
  <definition>Articles	means the Articles of Association of the Company; </definition>
  <definition>Board	means the board of Directors for the time being of the Company; </definition>
  <definition>Change of Control	is as defined in the Articles; </definition>
  <definition>Director	means a director of the Company for the time being, including where applicable an alternate director; </definition>
  <definition>Investor	means <span_ucnum>JFDI.2014</span_ucnum> Pte. Ltd.; </definition>
  <definition>JFDI	also means <span_ucnum>JFDI.2014</span_ucnum> Pte. Ltd.; </definition>
<?if(data.term){?>  <definition>Maturity Date	<?=data.term?> from date of issue of the <?=data.security_type_short_singular?>, or such other date as may be mutually agreed between the Parties; </definition>
<?}?>
<?if(data.interest != undefined){?>
<definition>Interest Rate	The <?=data.security_type_short_singular?> <? if (data.interest > 0) { ?>accrues <?= data.interest ?>% simple interest, to be payable in full on the earlier of the Maturity Date or the date on which the <?=data.security_type_short_singular?> is converted or redeemed in full,<?}else{?>no interest.<?}?></definition>
<?}?>
  <definition>Trade Sale	means a sale of 75% or more of the voting share capital of the Company to a third party buyer; </definition>
  <definition>Memorandum	means the Memorandum of Association of the Company; </definition>
  <definition>Ordinary Shares	means the ordinary shares in the capital of the Company; </definition>
  <definition>Shares	means shares in the capital of the Company whether ordinary or preferred; </definition>
  <definition>S$ or $	means the lawful currency for the time being of the Republic of Singapore; and </definition>
  <para_1>Except where the context otherwise requires, words importing the singular include the plural and vice versa, words importing a gender include every gender and references to persons include bodies corporate or unincorporated, any state or any agency thereof and any other entity. </para_1>
  <para_1>Headings, marginal sidenotes, and graphic art are for ease of reference only and have no legal effect. Reference to Clauses are to Clauses of this Agreement and references to this Agreement include any amendments or supplementals thereto. </para_1>
  <para_1>Except where the context otherwise requires, references to any person include its successors and permitted assignees. Except where the context otherwise requires, Clauses which refer to the &#8220;Company&#8221; shall apply mutatis mutandis to subsidiaries or successors of the Company which may from time to time be established. </para_1>
  <para_1>References in this Agreement to a time of day are to Singapore time. </para_1>
  <para_1>This Agreement shall be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the Republic of Singapore. </para_1>
  <a_left_sidehead>Conditions Precedent </a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>The obligations of the parties under this agreement are conditional upon:&#8212; </numbered_2_para>
  <numbered_3_para>approvals and consents (including any governmental, regulatory and/or corporate approvals and consents) in the form and substance satisfactory to JFDI (where applicable), for the transactions contemplated under this agreement, being obtained and not withdrawn or amended, on or before the Completion Date; </numbered_3_para>
  <numbered_3_para>representations and warrants by the Company that all intellectual property and other rights necessary to pursue the business are the full legal, beneficial, and unencumbered property of the Company; and </numbered_3_para>
  <numbered_3_para>full and accurate disclosure by the Company of information used to calculate the valuation of the Company and JFDI&#8217;s shareholding percentage, consistent with JFDI&#8217;s valuation methodology, and consistent with previous representations and warrants by the Company made at the time of the signing of the Founder Agreement. </numbered_3_para>
</Story_Main>
</Root>
