<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Class F Preference Shares</b_left_sidehead_nonum>

<numbered_1_para override="numberingContinue=false numberingStartAt=<?= data._include.numberingStartAt ?>">The Company may issue preference shares in the capital of the Company (“Class F Shares”), at an issue price of <?= data.price_per_f_share || "S$0.01" ?> each or such other amount as the Directors may determine, which shall carry the following rights, benefits and privileges and be subject to the following restrictions:</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards issue. Class F Shares may be issued with the sanction of an ordinary resolution pursuant to agreements between the Company and individual holders (“Class F Agreements”), the terms of which the Directors may determine.
As regards redemption and restriction. The Company shall have the right to redeem Class F Shares. Redemption may occur at the issue price or such other price as the Directors may determine. The redemption right may be limited by Class F Agreements. Class F Shares which are subject to this right of redemption shall be known as Restricted F Shares. Class F Shares over which the Company has waived its right of redemption shall be known as Unrestricted F Shares.
As regards conversion. A Holder of Unrestricted F Shares shall have the right to convert those shares to ordinary shares at a one-for-one ratio at any time. Restricted F Shares may be converted only with the sanction of a special resolution of the Ordinary Shareholders.
As regards automatic conversion. In the event of a trade sale, in which 75% or more of the issued Ordinary share capital of the Company is sold to a third party buyer (a “Trade Sale”),</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_3_para>all Unrestricted Class F Shares shall automatically convert to ordinary shares at a one-for-one ratio, and
all Restricted Class F Shares shall be dealt with according to the Class F Agreements governing those shares or (if those agreements are silent on the matter) at the absolute discretion of the Directors.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards voting. Other than as provided for under the Act, the Holders of Unrestricted F Shares shall be entitled to vote on any matter in a general meeting of the Company, pari passu with holders of ordinary shares, and in the case of a poll their votes shall be counted according to the number of ordinary shares they would hold if all their Unrestricted F Shares were converted. For the avoidance of doubt, Restricted F Shares carry no voting rights.
As regards income. The Holders of Class F Shares shall not be entitled to participate in the profits of the Company available for distribution by way of dividend or otherwise.
As regards surplus profits and assets. The Holders of Class F Shares shall have no right to participate in the profits or assets or any distributions of proceeds of the Company beyond the rights conferred under this Article. 
As regards transfers, registration, register and replacement. Class F Shares will be in registered form and the Company shall maintain a register thereof. The provisions of these Articles relating to the registration, transfer, transmission, certificates and replacement thereof applicable to ordinary shares shall apply mutatis mutandis to Class F Shares subject to the terms of the Agreement.
As regards pre-emptive rights. Notwithstanding Article <?= data.aa_preemptive_clause_number || "41" ?>, the Company may issue new Class F Shares without first offering the new shares to existing Members.
As regards substitution securities. In the event of a Trade Sale, Change of Control event (as defined under “Additional Definitions” above), winding-up, or dissolution of the Company pursuant to reconstruction, amalgamation, merger or consolidation, the resultant corporate entity responsible for the liabilities of the Company with respect to Class F Shares shall issue such securities in substitution and replacement of Class F Shares and on such terms as shall be approved by at least 51% of all then existing Holders of Class F Shares unless the terms of such securities in substitution are no less favourable than the terms of Class F Shares in which case the approval by Holders of Class F Shares shall not be required.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_para>Save as provided above, there are no other anti-dilution or protective provisions in respect of the Class F Shares.
In the event of any conflict or inconsistency between the provisions of this Article and the other provisions of these Articles, then the provisions of this Article shall prevail.</numbered_2_para>
