<Root xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/" xmlns:aid5="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/5.0/">
<?!= include("inc_cover_standard_parties", data, {cover_title:"Articles of Association"}) ?>
<?!= include("inc_cover_jfdi", data, { in_series:"02" }) ?>
<Firstpage_Sidebar>
<sidebar>See statutes.agc.gov.sg Cap 50.</sidebar>
</Firstpage_Sidebar>
<Story_Main>
  <chapter_header>Articles of Association</chapter_header>
<para_1>Pursuant to Article 36 of the Companies Act (Cap. 50) of Singapore, <?= data.company.name ?> hereby adopts as its Articles of Association the regulations shown in Table A of the Fourth Schedule of that Act, with the following alterations:</para_1>

<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Rights of First Refusal in Transfer of Shares</b_left_sidehead_nonum>

<numbered_1_para override="numberingContinue=false numberingStartAt=20">Subject to these Regulations, any member may transfer all or any of his shares by instrument in writing in any usual or common form or in any other form which the directors may approve.</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_para>The instrument shall be executed by or on behalf of the transferor and the transferor shall remain the holder of the shares transferred until the transfer is registered and the name of the transferee is entered in the register of members in respect thereof.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>The restrictions set out in this article shall not apply to any transfer of shares in the following circumstances:</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>by any Member being a corporation of any shares to another corporation resulting from a reconstruction or amalgamation of such Member or to any subsidiary or holding company of such Member or to another subsidiary of such holding company;
by any Member to another Member, of which the written consent of the majority of the other non-purchasing members had been obtained; or
to which the consent in writing of all the Members within that class of shares for the time being is given.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_2_para>Subject to any direction to the contrary that may be given by the company in general meeting, all shares, before being offered for transfer to any person who is not a Member, shall first be offered, on the same terms, to such persons as at the date of the offer are entitled to receive notices from the company of general meetings in proportion, as nearly as the circumstances admit, to the amount of the existing shares to which they are entitled, first within their class of shares and then to Members of other classes. The offer shall be made via the Directors or the Corporate Secretary by notice specifying the number of shares offered, and limiting a time within which the offer, if not accepted, will be deemed to be declined, and, after the expiration of that time, or on the receipt of an intimation from the person to whom the offer is made that he declines to accept the shares offered, the directors may register the transfer of those shares as directed by the transferor.</numbered_2_para>

<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Notices</b_left_sidehead_nonum>

<numbered_1_para override="numberingContinue=false numberingStartAt=108">Notice may be given by the company to any member in person, by post, or by e-mail.</numbered_1_para>

<?!= include("jfdi_articles_additional_definitions", data, { numberingStartAt: data.aa_f_clause_number-1 } ) ?>
<?!= include("jfdi_articles_class_f",                data, { numberingStartAt: data.aa_f_clause_number } ) ?>

</Story_Main>
</Root>
