<Root xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/" xmlns:aid5="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/5.0/">
<?!= include("inc_cover_standard_parties", data, {cover_title:"Articles of Association"}) ?>
<?!= include("inc_cover_jfdi", data, { in_series:"02" }) ?>
<Firstpage_Sidebar>
<sidebar>See statutes.agc.gov.sg Cap 50.</sidebar>
</Firstpage_Sidebar>
<Story_Main>
  <chapter_header>Articles of Association</chapter_header>
<para_1>Pursuant to Article 36 of the Companies Act (Cap. 50) of Singapore, <?= data.company.name ?> hereby adopts as its Articles of Association the regulations shown in Table A of the Fourth Schedule of that Act, with the following alterations:</para_1>

<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Rights of First Refusal in Transfer of Shares</b_left_sidehead_nonum>

<numbered_1_para override="numberingContinue=false numberingStartAt=20">Subject to these Regulations, any member may transfer all or any of his shares by instrument in writing in any usual or common form or in any other form which the directors may approve.</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_para>The instrument shall be executed by or on behalf of the transferor and the transferor shall remain the holder of the shares transferred until the transfer is registered and the name of the transferee is entered in the register of members in respect thereof.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>The restrictions set out in this article shall not apply to any transfer of shares in the following circumstances:</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>by any Member being a corporation of any shares to another corporation resulting from a reconstruction or amalgamation of such Member or to any subsidiary or holding company of such Member or to another subsidiary of such holding company;
by any Member to another Member, of which the written consent of the majority of the other non-purchasing members had been obtained; or
to which the consent in writing of all the Members within that class of shares for the time being is given.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_2_para>Subject to any direction to the contrary that may be given by the company in general meeting, all shares, before being offered for transfer to any person who is not a Member, shall first be offered, on the same terms, to such persons as at the date of the offer are entitled to receive notices from the company of general meetings in proportion, as nearly as the circumstances admit, to the amount of the existing shares to which they are entitled, first within their class of shares and then to Members of other classes. The offer shall be made via the Directors or the Corporate Secretary by notice specifying the number of shares offered, and limiting a time within which the offer, if not accepted, will be deemed to be declined, and, after the expiration of that time, or on the receipt of an intimation from the person to whom the offer is made that he declines to accept the shares offered, the directors may register the transfer of those shares as directed by the transferor.</numbered_2_para>

<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Notices</b_left_sidehead_nonum>

<numbered_1_para override="numberingContinue=false numberingStartAt=108">Notice may be given by the company to any member in person, by post, or by e-mail.</numbered_1_para>

<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Class F Preference Shares</b_left_sidehead_nonum>

<numbered_1_para override="numberingContinue=false numberingStartAt=114">The Company may issue preference shares in the capital of the Company (“Class F Shares”), at an issue price of S$1 each or such other amount as the Directors may determine, which shall carry the following rights, benefits and privileges and be subject to the following restrictions:­--</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards issue. Class F Shares may be issued with the sanction of an ordinary resolution pursuant to agreements between the Company and individual holders (“Class F Agreements”), the terms of which the Directors may determine.
As regards redemption and restriction. The Company shall have the right to redeem Class F Shares. Redemption may occur at the issue price or such other price as the Directors may determine. The redemption right may be limited by Class F Agreements. Class F Shares which are subject to this right of redemption shall be known as Restricted F Shares. Class F Shares over which the Company has waived its right of redemption shall be known as Unrestricted F Shares.
As regards conversion. A Holder of Unrestricted F Shares shall have the right to convert those shares to ordinary shares at a one-for-one ratio at any time. Restricted F Shares may be converted only with the sanction of a special resolution of the Ordinary Shareholders.
As regards automatic conversion. In the event of a trade sale, in which 75% or more of the issued Ordinary share capital of the Company is sold to a third party buyer (a “Trade Sale”),</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_3_para>all Unrestricted Class F Shares shall automatically convert to ordinary shares at a one-for-one ratio, and
all Restricted Class F Shares shall be dealt with according to the Class F Agreements governing those shares or (if those agreements are silent on the matter) at the absolute discretion of the Directors.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards voting. Other than as provided for under the Act, the Holders of Unrestricted F Shares shall be entitled to vote on any matter in a general meeting of the Company, pari passu with holders of ordinary shares, and in the case of a poll their votes shall be counted according to the number of ordinary shares they would hold if all their Unrestricted F Shares were converted. For the avoidance of doubt, Restricted F Shares carry no voting rights.
As regards income. The Holders of Class F Shares shall not be entitled to participate in the profits of the Company available for distribution by way of dividend or otherwise.
As regards surplus profits and assets. The Holders of Class F Shares shall have no right to participate in the profits or assets or any distributions of proceeds of the Company beyond the rights conferred under this Article. 
As regards transfers, registration, register and replacement. Class F Shares will be in registered form and the Company shall maintain a register thereof. The provisions of these Articles relating to the registration, transfer, transmission, certificates and replacement thereof applicable to ordinary shares shall apply mutatis mutandis to Class F Shares subject to the terms of the Agreement.
As regards pre-emptive rights. Notwithstanding Article 41, the Company may issue new Class F Shares without first offering the new shares to existing Members.
As regards substitution securities. In the event of a Trade Sale, Change of Control event (as defined under “Additional Definitions” below), winding-up, or dissolution of the Company pursuant to reconstruction, amalgamation, merger or consolidation, the resultant corporate entity responsible for the liabilities of the Company with respect to Class F Shares shall issue such securities in substitution and replacement of Class F Shares and on such terms as shall be approved by at least 51% of all then existing Holders of Class F Shares unless the terms of such securities in substitution are no less favourable than the terms of Class F Shares in which case the approval by Holders of Class F Shares shall not be required.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_para>Save as provided above, there are no other anti-dilution or protective provisions in respect of the Class F Shares.
In the event of any conflict or inconsistency between the provisions of this Article and the other provisions of these Articles, then the provisions of this Article shall prevail.</numbered_2_para>
</Story_Main>
</Root>
